(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-01T02:05:54.505403",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Peafowl of the Blue Flame
Pavolia Reine
Anya Melfissa
Kobo Kanaeru
Moona Hoshinova
Kureiji Ollie
Tsunomaki Watame
Takanashi Kiara
Nerissa Ravencroft
Iida Pochi.
Peafowl of the Blue Flame
KiLLKiSS
弄ばれて
Trifled with,
垂れ流す
and leaked...
音のない音は
this soundless sound
遍く
reaches everywhere.
名前を捨てたのね
You cast away your name, didn't you?
あなたのモザイクが泣いてる
Your mosaic is weeping.
can not, can not, not, not, not deny
紛れもなく真実
...it is unmistakably the truth.
さあ預けて 回帰するように
Now, entrust it to me, as if returning.
エネルギーはサイクル そういまは
Energy is a cycle, so now...
無重力 象徴的なパレード
...is a weightless, symbolic parade.
この月夜に 仰げば仰げ
Under this moonlit night, the more you look up...
completeness ss'
...the completeness is shown.
嗚呼 命の灯を掲げ
Ah, hold up the light of life!
KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS jude KiLLKiSS juda
欺いて
Deceive me...
KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS jude KiLLKiSS juda
抱きしめて
...and hold me tight.
ねえ 無防備だね
Hey, you are so defenseless.
美しい戯れに
In this beautiful playfulness,
人は壊れてゆく
people gradually break down.
可笑しいわね
How amusing.
'cuz we're all alone
噛み締めてもまだ痛むなら
If it still hurts even when you bite down...
手を挙げ 希え
...then raise your hands and pray.
oh, when you bleed, 惑星にそう
Oh, when you bleed, towards the planet...
その影を伸ばせ
...stretch that shadow.
ねえ 私の世界が 知りたがっているわ さあ
Hey, my world wants to know. Come on.
you bleed, yes bleed, その血で
You bleed, yes, bleed. With that blood,
天の五線譜を書き換えれば
if you rewrite heaven's musical staff...
code \"KiLLKiSS\" uh...
KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS jude KiLLKiSS juda
欺いて
Deceive me...
KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS jude KiLLKiSS juda
抱きしめて
...and hold me tight.
ねえ あからさまだね
Hey, it is so obvious.
醜い終局に
To this ugly end,
すべてが変わってゆく
everything is changing.
儚いのね
How fleeting it is.
そう このまま
Yes, just like this...
壊れて
...broken.
ラリラリララ ラリラ
Lalilalilala lalila
CR詠ZY
BREAK AWAY BREAK AWAY 細胞レベル
BREAK AWAY, BREAK AWAY on a cellular level.
割に不本意 感情乱れてる
Somewhat reluctant, my emotions are in disarray.
姿仕草滑稽でしょう
My appearance and gestures are ridiculous, right?
DON'T YOU THINK? DON'T YOU THINK?
I'M SO LAZY 多分そう
I'M SO LAZY, probably so.
FINE SOUND 並べてるだけの人
FINE SOUND, just a person lining them up.
TRASH TRASH TOSS AWAY
TRASH, TRASH, TOSS IT AWAY!
DON'T YOU THINK? DON'T YOU THINK?
IN THIS WORLD この頭には
IN THIS WORLD, inside this head...
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL 舞い散る花びら
...WHAT A BEAUTIFUL dance of scattering petals.
BALALAIKA 飲みたいね
BALALAIKA, I want to drink it.
ラリラリララ ラリラ
Lalilalilala lalila
誰もが抱いた
Everyone has harbored it...
C-R-A-Z-Y
一瞬の感情に RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON
RIDE ON, RIDE ON, RIDE ON, RIDE ON a fleeting emotion!
心は95
My heart is at 95%.
狂気のSAMURAI
A SAMURAI of madness.
血走らせた目で 引くくらい READY TO DIE
With bloodshot eyes, enough to back off, READY TO DIE.
陽は昇り あなたの空 真っ黒な空
The sun rises into your sky, a pitch-black sky.
荒々しく引きちぎって
Wildly tear it apart.
ほらその場所で 聞こえてくる鼓動の仕掛け
Look, right there, the mechanism of the heartbeat can be heard.
轟くのは己の調べ 誰かのじゃない己の調べ
What roars is my own melody, not someone else's, but my own.
タッタッタラタッタッタ
Ta-ta-ta-ra-ta-ta-ta
目の前に広がる
The world that stretches
世界はブルー
before me is blue,
ひとまず
so for now,
さあ move move
come on, move, move.
speak about 生き方
Speak about our way of life,
There's no need
何をそんなに張り切ってえらそうに
Why are you so worked up and acting so high and mighty?
ah give me more 愛を
Ah, give me more love.
ah 右も左も
Ah, turn right, turn left,
知りもしないで言わないで
don't talk without knowing a thing.
Don't you think? Don't you think?
ニヤリ影が笑う
The shadow smiles with a smirk.
世界は大体
The world is mostly
C-R-A-Z-Y
繰り返すように
As if to repeat it,
ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
分かってもいない
You don't even understand,
アレコレ authorize
authorizing this and that.
Tell me something for the new
偉大な期待の時代のバイブル
a bible for this era of great expectations.
clap back!
losin' my mind, shooting my side
Losing my mind, shooting my side.
save it あなたのその瞬間
Save it, that moment of yours,
maybe nothing wrong, nothing wrong
maybe nothing's wrong, nothing's wrong.
La-dee-la-lee-la-la la-lee-la
誰もが大体
Everyone is mostly
C-R-A-Z-Y
一瞬の感情に
To a momentary emotion,
ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
心は95
My heart is at 95,
狂気のサムライ
a crazy samurai.
血走らせた目で引くくらい
Drawing back with bloodshot eyes,
Ready to die
ハロー 日は昇り
Hello, the sun rises,
あなたの空 真っ黒な空
in your sky, your pitch black sky.
荒々しく引きちぎって
Violently tearing it apart.
ほら その場所で
Look, right in that place,
聞こえてくる鼓動の仕掛け
the mechanism of the beating heart can be heard.
驚くのはまだこれから まだこれから
It's still too early to be surprised, still too early.
あぁ もう待ちわびて
Ah, I'm already tired of waiting,
時計の針 零時の街
clock hands pointing to midnight in the city.
猛々しくいざ
Fiercely, now,
Raise your voice
ほら すぐそこで
Look, right over there,
始まり出す孤高 of the 宴
the solitary feast begins.
奏でるのは己の調べ
What is playing is my own melody,
唯一無二の己の調べ
my one and only melody.
わーい！
Wheee!
Perhatian, sang putri merak yang tertiup angin, Pavolia Reine dari Hololive ID!
Attention, please! The wind-blown peacock princess, Pavolia Reine from Hololive ID!
Attention, please! I'm Reine from Hololive ID Generation 2!
皆様ごきげんよう、私ホロライブインドネシア2期生、パヴォリア・レイネと申しますの！
Good day, everyone! I am Pavolia Reine from Hololive Indonesia Gen 2!
And welcome to Pavolia Reine's... Peafowl of the Blue Flame!
Yay! Pavolia Reine's 2025 Birthday! Welcome!
いえーい、ようこそ！
Yay, welcome!
えーと、左上にハッシュタグがありまして。
So, there's a hashtag in the upper-left corner.
It reads #ReineMEPtember2025, which is pretty much the same hashtag I've been using for the past like few years, yeah?
It reads #ReineMEPtember2025, which is pretty much the same hashtag I've been using for the past few years, yeah?
And if you guys have any thoughts throughout the live, anything, you can write it, and I'll be looking forward to them.
お、ご感想 and everything, you guys can write...
Yes, your thoughts and everything, you guys can write...
ちゃんぷるーちゃんぷるーで喋るね。あー、ま、いいや、とりあえず。
I'm speaking in a mix of languages. Ah, well, whatever, anyway.
I'm excited to know what you guys think of the live. You don't have to write it now, 今じゃなくても大丈夫です。
I'm excited to know what you guys think of the live. You don't have to write it now, it's fine if it's not right now.
But, I will be waiting, yeah! So just put any of your thoughts in the hashtag, okay?
And next, I want to talk about the concept of the stage. Look at this! It's so cool, right?
There's a mysterious flame, mysterious locks, mysterious...
...cans, mysterious...
Where's the liquid? Well, there was like a blue liquid there, but I mean you saw it, right? Yeah, haha!
If you, um, I guess if you think of fire or flame, you know,
usually you guys think of the color red, right, automatically? そうですね、あの、火といえばですね、赤のイメージが強いかもしれませんが、
usually you guys think of the color red, right, automatically? Indeed, when you think of fire, the image of red might be strong,
um, but actually, the blue flame is the strongest, ya enggak sih?
but actually, the blue flame is the strongest, isn't it?
But actually, 実はですね、青い炎の方が一番強い。
But actually, the truth is, a blue flame is the strongest.
と思います。Yeah!
I think so. Yeah!
So that's the theme of today's birthday. I want to show you guys just how hot a blue flame can be through...
hot songs, and songs that will make you feel, aduh, gerah banget, so hot, so...
hot songs, and songs that will make you feel, oh my god, so hot, so hot, so...
...phew, gitu! Pokoknya, just look forward to it, okay?
...phew, like that! Anyway, just look forward to it, okay?
And the songs we've sang today, uh, we have two songs. The first one was 'Kill Kiss'. そうですね、すごく好きな
And the songs we've sung today, we have two songs. The first one was 'Kill Kiss'. Yes, a song I really love...
曲で、Ave Mujica様の「Kill Kiss」です。
which is 'Kill Kiss' by Ave Mujica-sama.
And then, 2曲目は、私がすごい大好きなあのプロセカのユニット、Vivid BAD SQUAD様の「CRaZY」でした！
And then, the second song was 'CRaZY' by the Project Sekai unit I love so much, Vivid BAD SQUAD!
And the second song was 'CRaZY' from a unit I really really like from Proseka, by Vivid BAD SQUAD. I hope you guys enjoyed it!
Yeah!
Emang kayak Reine tuh suka banget gitu sama lagunya, haha!
It's because Reine really loves that song, haha!
Jadi, masih akan ada lebih banyak lagi. There's gonna be way more, more, more, more songs,
So, there's going to be even more. There's gonna be way more, more, more, more songs,
and I'm sure there's a lot of guests. I hope you guys are excited for them!
これからもね、もっともっと熱くなるからね、ゲストも...
From here on too, it's going to get hotter and hotter, and guests too...
many, many, many, many, many! So, please look forward to it!
But for now, I'm gonna sing one of my original songs.
Do you guys know what it is?
The next song is... Love Me Love Me.
そっと 君のとなり
Softly next to you,
じっと 見てるばかり
I just keep staring.
愛 愛 やまない雨
In love, love, this endless rain
世界に二人きり
drenches our world of just two.
延々 キスをするように 深層
Kissing you forever, deep down...
そう 今この手に
Yes, now in this hand...
となりたささえも 愛の形
Even the wish to be together is a shape of love.
運命的に結ばれた 小指 ふわ握る
Tying our destined pinkies, I hold it softly.
約束をしよう
Let's make a promise.
Love me, love me
私しかいらない
You only need me.
Love me, love me
君しかいらない
I only need you.
ギュッと 抱きしめあったら
If we hold each other tight,
きっと 逃げられない
surely we cannot escape.
Tick tack 針が回る
Tick tack, the clock hands spin,
世界に二人きり、ね
just the two of us in this world, right?
キスを交わすように 感傷
A sentimental feeling, like exchanging kisses.
欲しい、焦がしてよ
I want it, make it burn,
どんな 悲鳴さえも 愛の メロディ
even any scream is a melody of love.
運命的に結ばれた 小指 ふわ握る
Tying our destined pinkies, I hold it softly.
約束をしよう
Let's make a promise.
Love me, love me
私しかいらない
You only need me.
Love me, love me
君しかいらない
I only need you.
愛して
Love me,
愛されて
and let yourself be loved.
離れられない
We can't be apart,
You and me
二人きりで
just the two of us.
Give me
your love
願うほど
The more I wish,
したたる赤い糸
the dripping red string of fate,
何もかも
everything,
全て失う
I will lose it all.
愛を
Love,
もっと
more,
頂戴
give me.
私しかいらない
You only need me.
Love me, love me
君しかいらない
I only need you.
Love me, love me
ファイアダンス
[Title: Fire Dance]
まあ こんなもんでいいか
Well, I guess this is good enough.
そろそろヤメにしようや
It's about time to call it quits.
手抜き 手に入れた無理
Cutting corners and forcing my way through,
それを大事にすんのがオマエの売り
treasuring that is your selling point.
いつか来る後悔
The regret that will come someday,
隠せるかは今の自分次第
whether you can hide it depends on your current self.
やるだけやったれ
Just do what you can,
誰々じゃなくて未来の自分に嫌われないように
not for someone else, but so your future self won't hate you.
比べてしまうの？ ダサッ、か
Are you comparing yourself? How uncool.
目の前を塞ぐ壁、だから何？
A wall blocking your way, so what?
不満不平それだけで結構
Complaints and grievances, that's enough of that.
あとはひたすら前に進むだけ、Yeah
All that's left is to just keep moving forward, yeah!
バカにされればされるほどに
The more we are made fun of,
この高鳴りが爽快だろう？
isn't this pounding heart exhilarating?
もっといけるはず
We should be able to go further.
まだやれるはず
We can still keep going!
ヤッパッパッラッパッパ 燃え上がらすファイアダンス
Ya-pa-pa, ra-pa-pa, let the fire dance blaze up!
歌え 踊れ 騒げ つかビビってんのか、ハァ？
Sing, dance, make noise! Wait, are you scared, huh?
ヤッパッパッラッパッパ かっ飛ばす場外
Ya-pa-pa, ra-pa-pa, hit it out of the park!
自分で決めた限界なんて 挑戦、エチケットじゃん
A limit you set yourself is just etiquette for challenging yourself!
そうそうそうそう 逃げんの？その感じで保存
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, running away like that?
No No No No いいの？そのアンサー
No, no, no, no, is that answer okay?
届け 限界超え行く衝動
Reach out, the urge to exceed limits!
音の鳴る方へ
Towards where the sound is playing!
ヤッパッパッラッパッパ 燃え上がらすファイアダンス
Ya-pa-pa, ra-pa-pa, let the fire dance blaze up!
歌え 踊れ 騒げ 舞い上がれメラメラ
Sing, dance, make noise! Blaze up, flare up!
Tolerate!
Ad-ad-ad-ad...
ガンガン昇る今何度？
Steadily rising, what's the temperature now?
5万2千3百ポイント超常現象
A paranormal phenomenon at 52,300 points!
何があったってもれなくもれなく
No matter what happens, without exception,
どんどん進め
keep moving forward,
見せてる好回転
showing off this great spin!
アリーに砂糖 テイラーが本番
Sugar for the ants, Taylor takes the main stage!
手拍子手のひら返しはロマン
Clapping along to a sudden change of heart is romance!
重ねる努力から血を流す ゲロン！
Bleeding from piled up effort, get on!
Hey-oh!
ヤッパッパッパッパッパッパ
Yappappappappappappa,
ぶっ放すバンダ
blasting away with the band!
さあ歌え 踊れ 騒げ
Now sing, dance, make some noise!
スカビビってんの？ ハハッ
Are you scared? Haha!
ヤッパッパッパッパッパッパ
Yappappappappappappa,
かっ飛ばす障害
blasting through obstacles!
頭で決めてる限界なんて
A limit decided only in your head...
当然言ってんじゃん パー
Of course, that's just nonsense!
100% イラつくの勘違い
100%, getting annoyed is a misunderstanding!
100% 笑顔のアンチ
100%, smiling haters!
降伏に気が狂う初期衝動
The primal urge that drives me crazy into submission,
音の鳴る方へ
towards where the sound is playing!
ヤッパッパッパッパッパッパ
Yappappappappappappa,
ぶっ放すバンダ
blasting away with the band!
さあ歌え 踊れ 騒げ
Now sing, dance, make some noise!
上がれ マナマナ
Rise up, mana-mana!
Tolerate!
ヤッパッパッパッパッパッパ
Yappappappappappappa,
ぶっ放すバンダ
blasting away with the band!
段違いにハイに 追いついてハイに
Getting high on a whole different level, catch up and get high!
撫でるも最狂 ラストイン怪美
Even caressing is the craziest, the final mysterious beauty!
ヤッパッパッパッパッパッパ
Yappappappappappappa,
かっ飛ばす障害
blasting through obstacles!
お助けください 乗り出すゴッド
Please save me, the god stepping in,
パパパッスンアッパー パパパッスンパーティー
Pa-pa-pass-on upper, pa-pa-pass-on party!
100% イラつくの勘違い
100%, getting annoyed is a misunderstanding!
100% 笑顔のアンチ
100%, smiling haters!
降伏に気が狂う初期衝動
The primal urge that drives me crazy into submission,
音の鳴る方へ
towards where the sound is playing!
ヤッパッパッパッパッパッパ
Yappappappappappappa,
ぶっ放すバンダ
blasting away with the band!
さあ歌え 踊れ 騒げ
Now sing, dance, make some noise!
上がれ マナマナ
Rise up, mana-mana!
Tolerate!
Ad-ad-ad-ad...
夜の始まりさ
The yearnin' luna hiding from sorrow,
bunny girl
誘惑されることに
You got my heartbeat running away
弾け飛ぶことに愛を乾杯
Cheers to bittersweet romance, my worries are popping
伝えられなくても
Even if I can't tell this to you
恋の始まりさ
Coiled around your ripening heart,
bunny girl
誰かを穿って
Love-starved silhouette came closer
澄んだ君の目を 孕んで
Your glassy eyes sink in blue, I'll carry it
さあ
Hey,
キザなステップを刻んで
shall we sashay posh steps, I say
仕事帰りの疲れは
Your work fatigue melts away
私と このグラスに
Into my glass as fading the day
さあ
Hey,
自分好みに纏って
you can stay true to own groove
世間に対する気持ち
Won't you try to pour your feels you've been having
私に注いでみない？
to toxic group?
ありがちなラブソングでも
Although it's just a typical love song
愛が込められてるの
True feelings make it beat so strong
それでも汚れるのね
Just a glance at you reveals it all,
君を見れば分かるの
your stains tell a story, can't help to fall
下を向く君の目を
I won't chase your hidden dull sights though
無理矢理剥ごうとはしない
Force the darkness into my lights, you know
だから そんな顔せず
In my warmth, you'll surely find it
手を差し伸べて
All the peace you have left behind,
ほら
c'mon
夜の始まりさ
The yearnin' luna hiding from sorrow,
bunny girl
誘惑されることに
You got my heartbeat running away
弾け飛ぶことに愛を乾杯
Cheers to bittersweet romance, my worries are popping
伝えられなくても
Even if I can't tell this to you
恋の始まりさ
Coiled around your ripening heart,
bunny girl
誰かを穿って
Love-starved silhouette came closer
澄んだ君の目を 孕んで
Your glassy eyes sink in blue, I'll carry it
君の愛を知った気でハイになっていて
I thought I know your love tonight, fade away and fight in the darkest night
感度去っていて 毎度泣いていてさ
Every time you just cry
それくらいがいいんでしょ
Always low-key and being like that?
さあ
Hey,
キザなステップを刻んで
shall we sashay posh steps, I say
君の顔色今では
For sure, the shade of your weary face
マシになってきてるから
Has found a much healthier place
君に委ねるわ
Into your heart gently fall,
bunny girl
私をあげるわ
To you, I give my heart, my all,
bunny girl
誘惑される鼓動に
You got my heartbeat running away
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
Cheers to bittersweet romance, my worries are popping
伝えられてるはず
I know what I can tell this to you
夜の始まりさ
The yearnin' luna hiding from sorrow,
bunny girl
誰かを穿って
Love-starved silhouette came closer
澄んだ君の目を 孕んで
Your glassy eyes sink in blue, I'll carry it
ヤミ ヤミ ドゥ
Yummy, yummy, do...
ヤミ ヤミ ドゥ ドゥ
Yummy, yummy, do-do...
ヤベェ病まない悩みやヤム All Night Show
Gosh, these endless worries, a sickness eating at me all night show.
ヤミヤムヤミ
[Title: Yummy Yum Yummy]
放心調子？なんだって徘徊曖昧シャットダウン
Absentminded state? Whatever, wandering in ambiguous shutdown.
初頭のランウェイ 逃げ切りワンダー
Early runway, a getaway wonder.
急成長正常難題は movin' to 選択肢
Rapid growth, normal difficult problems are moving to options.
引っ込みダーウィンさぁ？ Won't you steal my heart?
Introverted Darwin, huh? Won't you steal my heart?
ヤミ ヤミ ドゥ
Yummy, yummy, do...
ヤミ ヤミ ドゥ ドゥ
Yummy, yummy, do-do...
ヤミ ヤミ ドゥ
Yummy, yummy, do...
衝動現実からの escape
Escaping from impulsive reality...
のらりくらり S-O-S なら
idling along. If it's an SOS...
燃え上がるわ全身
my entire body blazes up.
よくばりピーポー yummy, yummy ジャスティス
Greedy people, yummy, yummy justice.
One chance 狙う jackpot
One chance to aim for the jackpot...
願いまーす gabut
I wish for it, chomp!
のるかそるか kill or ill の look back show!
Sink or swim, kill or ill look back show!
観戦？完成？貸せ！貸せ！
Spectating? Complete? Give it! Give it!
おすそ分け？
Share some with me?
ah, ズッキンズッキンパラッパ冷めないうちに
Ah, throbbing, throbbing, pa-ra-pa, before it cools down...
ヤミ ヤミ ドゥ
Yummy, yummy, do...
ah, ズッキンズッキンパラッパお味はいかが？
Ah, throbbing, throbbing, pa-ra-pa, how does it taste?
ヤミ ヤミ ドゥ
Yummy, yummy, do...
ah, 足りない まだ足りないの
Ah, it's not enough, it's still not enough.
ヤミ ヤミ ドゥ
Yummy, yummy, do...
ah, lonely night まだ足りないの？
Ah, lonely night, is it still not enough?
最高 臨界 点 更新 中
Updating the highest critical point.
思考のマリアージュ駆け足ドメスティック
Marriage of thoughts, a rapid domestic.
右か左か 逃げるが先だ
Right or left, escaping comes first.
暴走道中 dug-dug, ガラ空きの dancehall
Rampaging on the way, thump-thump, in a completely empty dancehall.
卵が先だ ピースは揃った！
The egg comes first, all the pieces are here!
sir, baby, baby, baby, もう時間がないわ
Sir, baby, baby, baby, there's no more time.
ヤミ ヤミ ヤミ
Yummy, yummy, yummy...
ラリルララルーリ捕まえてルルーラ
Ra-ri-ru-ra-ra-ru-ri, catch me, ru-ru-ra...
壊れる前に
before it breaks.
ah, ドッキンドッキンパヤッパ ルージュを付けて
Ah, pounding, pounding, pa-ya-pa, putting on lipstick...
ヤミ ヤミ ドゥ
Yummy, yummy, do...
ah, ドッキンドッキンパヤッパ シンクロニズム
Ah, pounding, pounding, pa-ya-pa, synchronism.
ヤミ ヤミ ドゥ
Yummy, yummy, do...
ah, party time まだ足りないわ
Ah, party time, it's still not enough.
ヤミ ヤミ ドゥ
Yummy, yummy, do...
ah, 範囲外 もう消えそうだ
Ah, out of range, about to fade away.
こっち向いてよ 哀・二重
Look over here, sorrowful double.
クワック
Quack!
キャットラビング
[Title: Cat Loving]
痛いことは嫌いですが
I hate painful things,
君の手のひらは嫌いじゃない
but I don't hate the palm of your hand.
言葉はアメダマみたいに
Words are like candy,
甘く広がって 心満たす
spreading sweetly to fill my heart.
あぁ 全然わかってない
Ah, you don't understand at all.
永遠に言う通り
Just as you always say,
完全にフェアじゃない
it's not completely fair.
どこにいても
(Wherever you are)
あぁ なんでわかってない
Ah, why don't you understand?
元々あの子みたいに可愛くならなくちゃ
I should have been cute like her from the start.
愛情はそう何着
Love is, yes, how many outfits?
個数は how many?
Just how many in quantity?
もう耐えられないのだって わからなくなる
Because I can't bear it anymore, I'm losing track.
延命 またたび 週にのご褒美
Prolonging life, catnip, a weekly reward.
もう嫌になって あのすれ違わないように
I'm sick of this, so we don't pass each other by.
調子だってちゃんとなんない その毛繕い
I'm not feeling well, that grooming...
ニャッたよこにするから愛して
I'll lie down beside you, so love me.
Everybody to dance, it's a loving cat
Get it, get it, this is my courtship
Any, any, any time is fine with me
Give me, give me your love, my darling
痛いお間違いなんて みんなは言う
"A painful mistake," everyone says,
取り憑かれているって
saying that I'm possessed.
ならこの胸で美しく締め付けるような
Then what is this pain that beautifully tightens in my chest,
切なさはなんなの
feeling so sorrowful?
選ぶ言葉 戸惑う指先
My chosen words, my hesitant fingertips,
隠せないよこがお
and my profile that I can't hide...
私しか知らない
Only I know them.
わがままご機嫌も もしかして
Even your selfish mood, perhaps...
今日は優しく撫でてくれるのかな
Will you gently stroke me today?
躍らせてマイン
Make me dance, mine
柑橘の匂いだって凌ぐのだ
I'll even overcome the citrus scent
ほらもう 飼ったら 叱られるだけだし
Look, if you keep me, you'll just get scolded
今日だって ちゃんと お膝で おとなしく
Today too, I'll sit properly and quietly on your lap
にゃんと お好きなように ガブッと噛んで
and with a "meow", bite me hard however you like
「はい喜んで」
"Yes, gladly!"
「あなた方の為」
"For your sake"
「はい謹んで」
"Yes, respectfully"
「あなた方の為」
"For your sake"
差し伸びてきた手
The hand reached out
さながら正義仕立て
Just like a tailored justice
嫌嫌で生き延びて
Reluctantly surviving
わからずやに盾
Shielding against the stubborn
「はい喜んであなた方の為に」
"Yes, gladly for your sake"
「出来ることなら出来るとこまで」
"As much as possible, as far as I can go"
あと一歩を踏み出して
Take one more step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remember the bad things
奈落音頭奏でろ ドンドン
Play the rhythm of the abyss, boom, boom
もう一歩を踏み出して
Take one more step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remember the bad things
鳴らせ君の3から6マス トントントンツーツーツートントン
Sound your 3 to 6 spaces, dit-dit-dit, dah-dah-dah, dit-dit-dit
ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance
（踊れ）
(Dance)
ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance
（もっと鳴らせ）
(Make more sound)
ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance
（踊れ）
(Dance)
ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance
（もっと鳴らせ）
(Make more sound)
慣らせ君の病の町を
Accustom your diseased town
ドンドン
Boom, boom
隠せ笑える他人のオピニオン
Hide the laughable opinions of others
ドンドン
Boom, boom
うっちゃれ正義の超人たちを
Throw away the supermen of justice
ドンドン
Boom, boom
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス トントントントン ツーツーツートントン
Sound your 3 to 6 spaces, dit-dit-dit, dah-dah-dah, dit-dit-dit
怒り抱いても 優しさが勝つあなたの
Even holding anger, your kindness wins
欠けたとこが希望
Your flawed parts are hope
Save this game, Mr. A
救われたのは僕のうちの1人で
The one who was saved was one of me
あと一歩を踏み出して
Take one more step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remember the bad things
奈落音頭奏でろ ドンドン
Play the rhythm of the abyss, boom, boom
もう一歩を踏み出して
Take one more step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remember the bad things
鳴らせ君の3から6マス
Sound your 3 to 6 spaces
分かれ道思うがまま Go To Earth
Go to Earth at the crossroads as you please
任せきりワガママな言葉塞げろ
Block your completely selfish words, but
奏でろハクナマタタの音は
Play it, the sound of Hakuna Matata is
トントントントン ツーツーツートントン
Dit-dit-dit, dah-dah-dah, dit-dit-dit
ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance
（踊れ）
(Dance)
ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance
（もっと鳴らせ）
(Make more sound)
ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance
（踊れ）
(Dance)
ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance
（もっと鳴らせ）
(Make more sound)
慣らせ君の病の町を
Accustom your diseased town
ドンドン
Boom, boom
隠せ笑える他人のオピニオン
Hide the laughable opinions of others
ドンドン
Boom, boom
うっちゃれ正義の超人たちを
Throw away the supermen of justice
ドンドン
Boom, boom
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス トントントントン ツーツーツートントン
Sound your 3 to 6 spaces, dit-dit-dit, dah-dah-dah, dit-dit-dit
「はい喜んで あなた方の為に」
Yes, gladly for your sake
「出来ることなら出来るとこまで」
As much as possible, as far as I can go
「はい謹んで あなた方の為に」
Yes, respectfully for your sake
「鳴らせ君の3から6マス トントントントンツーツーツートントン」
Sound your 3 to 6 spaces, dit-dit-dit, dah-dah-dah, dit-dit-dit
わーーー！わうわう！
Waaaaah! Wow wow!
アハハハ！
Ahahaha!
イェーーイ！
Yeeaaah!
飯田ぽちママ！
Iida Pochi-mama!
イェーイ！
Yeeaaah!
読者の皆様こんにちは。お疲れ様です、飯田ぽちです！
Hello to all readers. Thank you for your hard work, I'm Iida Pochi!
イェーイ！
Yeeaaah!
アハハハ！
Ahahaha!
ママに教えてもらった言葉で、お上品な言葉で自己紹介します！
I will introduce myself using the elegant words Mama taught me!
えー、皆様ごきげんよう。わたくしパヴォリア・レイネ... あ、ちょっと待って...
Uh, good day to you all. I am Pavolia Reine... Ah, wait a second...
あ、ごきげんよう。リセット、リセット。ごきげんよう、わたくし...
Ah, good day. Reset, reset. Good day, I am...
ホロライブインドネシア2期生、パヴォリア・レイネと申します。以後お見知り置きを！
Pavolia Reine of Hololive Indonesia 2nd Generation. Please do get to know me!
わーーー！パーフェクト！
Waaaah! Perfect!
はい、お嬢様でございます。お嬢様ですね、完全に。
Yes, quite the lady. A true lady, absolutely.
お嬢様！お嬢様配信。
Ojou-sama! An elegant lady's stream.
お嬢様ムービング？お嬢様... Yes, お嬢様ムービング。
Ojou-sama moving? Ojou-sama... Yes, Ojou-sama moving.
お嬢様ムービング。お嬢様ムービング。
Ojou-sama moving. Ojou-sama moving.
Yeah!
イェーーイ！うーーー！
Yeeaaah! Woooo!
レイネちゃん、
Reine-chan,
Selamat ulang tahun!
Terima kasih!
Happy birthday! おめでとう！
Happy birthday! Congratulations!
Woo! Thank you!
さっきは、キャットラビングを一緒に歌いました！
Earlier, we sang Cat Loving together!
歌いました！
We sang it!
いかがでしたでしょうか？
How was it?
イェーイ！
Yeah!
どうだった？踊れてた？
How was it? Were we dancing well?
Nice!
もう腰が...
My waist is already...
No!
マッサージ、マッサージ。背中？
Massage, massage. Your back?
肩、肩お願いします、肩。
My shoulders, please do my shoulders.
お嬢様マッサージ！トントン... あ、ありがとうございます。
An elegant lady's massage! Tap tap... Ah, thank you very much.
私もマッサージ欲しい！
I want a massage too!
はい、お嬢様凝ってますねー。ここですか？こちらですか？
Yes, you're quite stiff, My Lady. Is it here? Or over here?
ワハハ！イェーイ！
Wahaha! Yeah!
パーフェクトでございます。
It is absolutely perfect.
パーフェクト！
Perfect!
どうでしたか？
How was it?
Pochimama and Reine, No Bunny Girl!
Yay!
Wow, wow, wow, wow!
お嬢様ハイテンションで、今日も素晴らしいです。さすがです。
Our lady is in high spirits today as well. Great as expected.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Hari ini... today, bagaimana ya? Gimana ngomongnya?
Today... today, how should I say it?
Pochimama, did you guys see Pochimama's 3D debut last time?
そう、二人で私の3Dお披露目で、レイネちゃんと一緒に歌って踊りました。みなさん、見ていただけましたでしょうか？
Yes, we sang and danced together at my 3D debut. Did everyone watch it?
Yay! And because of that, today, I invited Pochimama to dance and sing on stage with me!
ありがとうございます！ Thank you so much for inviting me. ありがとう。
Thank you very much! Thank you so much for inviting me. Thank you.
No, thank you, thank you, thank you for coming! I had so much fun. めっちゃ楽しい。
No, thank you, thank you, thank you for coming! I had so much fun. It was so much fun!
ね、ね。
Right, right?
Jadi, apa ya? Ngomong apa ya? What should we talk about? If I remember Pochimama, I remember...
So, what should we talk about? If I remember Pochimama, I remember...
お嬢様。
Ojou-sama.
Because back then, I thought, gimana ya... I'm a princess, so I have to act like a princess.
Because back then, I thought, like, "I'm a princess, so I have to act like a princess."
Kay "Ojou-sama" dakara, Nihongo de apa sih? "Ojou-sama" ya, "Ojou-sama" acting hitsuyo hitsuyo gitu guys.
Since I'm an Ojou-sama, what's it in Japanese? Ojou-sama, yeah. An Ojou-sama acting is needed, guys.
でも、もうこれでパーフェクトです。さっきの動きで。
But you are already perfect with those movements earlier.
そう、そう、ジャンプで、OKです。こっちの動きで？ こっちで？ こっちでお嬢様？
Yes, yes, with that jump, it's okay. With this movement? This one? This is Ojou-sama?
こっちで、こっちで。これがHololive IDお嬢様？
This one, this one. Is this Hololive ID's Ojou-sama?
みなさんもお嬢様になりたい方はね、トントンしてください。
Everyone, those who want to become an Ojou-sama, please "tonton" (watch/imitate).
トントンってなんですか？ トントン... トントンあぱ？ トントン。
What is "tonton"? Tonton... watch what? Tonton.
真似してください！ そう。この動きがお嬢様ですよ！ うわぁ！
Please imitate! Yes. This movement is Ojou-sama! Whoa!
本当にいいですかね、これで？
Is this really okay?
ちなみに、あのネタバレになると思うんですが...
By the way, I think this might be a spoiler...
あの、今日のグッズはね、誕生日グッズはね、ぽちママが頑張りしました！ イェーイ！
but for today's birthday goods, Pochimama worked really hard on them! Yay!
書かせていただきました、みなさん！ ちゃんとグッズ紹介まで最後までしっかり見てくださいね。よろしくお願いいたします。
I was allowed to draw them, everyone! Please watch carefully until the end for the goods introduction. Thank you!
Pokoknya, katanya jangan ke mana-mana guys, pokoknya tunggu sampai akhir karena ada goods dari Pochimama-sensei.
Anyway, she said don't go anywhere, guys. Wait until the end because there are goods from Pochimama-sensei.
Kalian pasti tidak mau ketinggalan kan? Makanya tonton sampai habis, oke?
You definitely don't want to miss it, right? So watch until the end, okay?
Ya, gitu deh intinya. Kiw! Oke, kalau gitu, apa namanya? Thank you Pochimama for coming!
Yeah, that's the point. Kiw! Okay then, what's it? Thank you Pochimama for coming!
ありがとう！ Thank you! Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
このあともライブが続くので、楽しんでね！ イェーイ！
The live performance will continue after this, so enjoy! Yay!
イェーイ！
Yay!
これかけていく。
I'll run off.
アイスクリーム！
Ice cream!
教えて！ もっと あなた の 事
Teach me! More about you
(tell me more more more more. tell me more more more more.)
聞かせて！ もっと あなた の 声
Let me hear! More of your voice
(let me hear more more more. let me hear more more more.)
こんなドキドキもう抑え切れない
I can't hold back this excitement anymore
(all i need you. oh! all i need you.)
(all I need is you, oh! All I need is you.)
友達は卒業
Graduating from being friends
運命の私見つけて欲しいの
I want you to find the destined me
One 勇気を出して
One! Summon up your courage
Two 見つめる作戦
Two! The strategy of gazing
Three 瞳と目が合えば
Three! When our eyes meet
Four!
止められない
Unstoppable!
yeah yeah yeah この恋この愛で
Yeah yeah yeah, with this romance and love
melt melty 溶けちゃうよ
Melt, melty, I'm melting
ねぇ？ねぇ？ねぇ？気づいて "my darling"
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice me, my darling
届け！大好き！
Reach out! I love you!
オリーちゃん！ はーい！ 何が好き？
Ollie-chan! Yes! What do you like?
チョコミントよりも あ・な・た！
More than chocolate mint, I like you!
コボちゃん！ はーい！ 何が好き？
Kobo-chan! Yes! What do you like?
ストロベリーフレーバーよりも あ・な・た！
More than strawberry flavor, I like you!
レイネちゃん！ はーい！ 何が好き？
Reine-chan! Yes! What do you like?
クッキー＆クリームよりも あ・な・た！
More than cookies and cream, I like you!
みんな！ はーい！ 何が好き？
Everyone! Yes! What do you like?
もちろん大好き アイスクリーム！
Of course, we love Ice Cream!
Yeah Yeah Yeah コロコロコロ愛で
Yeah Yeah Yeah! With rolling, rolling love,
Melty Melty とけちゃうよ
Melty, melty, I'm melting away!
ねぇ ねぇ ねぇ 気づいて My darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling,
届け 大好き
Deliver it—I love you!
I-C-E L-O-V-E Ice Cream!
S-C-R-E-A-M Scream!
お願い 見つけて My darling
Please find me, my darling
お願い 気づいて My darling
Please notice me, my darling
勇気を出して
Plucking up my courage
近づく作戦
My strategy to get closer
ピピッとハートが触れて
Beep beep! Our hearts touch
もう 止められない
And now, I can't be stopped!
Yeah Yeah Yeah コロコロコロ愛で
Yeah Yeah Yeah! With rolling, rolling love,
Melty Melty とけちゃうよ
Melty, melty, I'm melting away!
ねぇ ねぇ ねぇ 気づいて My darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling,
それはあなた
That person is you!
I-C-E L-O-V-E Ice Cream!
S-C-R-E-A-M Scream!
La La La...
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
Because in reality, I'm crazy
白鳥たちはそう
Just like all the swans
見えないとこでバタ足するんです
They are paddling where you can't see
本能に従順 忠実
Obedient and loyal to instinct
翻弄も重々承知
Fully aware of being tossed about
前途洋々だし…
And with a bright future ahead...
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
So that's why I take a break now and then
Don't say "lazy" / 作詞: 大森祥子 / 作曲: 前澤寛之
[Song: Don't say "lazy" / Lyrics: Shoko Omori / Music: Hiroyuki Maezawa]
この目でしっかり見定めて
I'll check clearly with my own eyes
行き先地図上マークして
And mark my destination on the map
近道あればそれが王道
If there's a shortcut, that's the way to go
はしょれる翼もあれば上等
If I have wings to skip steps, even better
ヤバ 爪割れた グルーで補修した
Oh no, I broke a nail! Fixed it with glue
それだけでなんか達成感
Just that gives me a sense of accomplishment
大切なのは自分 かわいがること
The important thing is to pamper yourself
自分を愛さなきゃ 他人も愛せない
If you don't love yourself, you can't love others
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
Because in reality, I'm crazy
能ある鷹はそう
Just like a skilled hawk
見えないとこにピック隠すんです
It hides its pick where you can't see
想像に一生懸命
Devoting my life to imagination
現実は絶体絶命
While reality is a desperate situation
発展途上だし…
We're still in development...
だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
So that's why my pitch suddenly goes off
その目に映らないだけだって
Even if it's just not visible in your eyes
やる気はメーター振り切って
My motivation is off the charts
いつでも全力で夢見て
Always dreaming with all my might
その分全力で眠って
And sleeping with all my might in return
ヤリ ちょい痩せた 調子づいて喰った
Yay, I lost a bit of weight! Got excited and overate
それだけでなんで？敗北感
Just because of that, why this sense of defeat?
すかさずに目標 下方修正して
Instantly revising my goals downward
柔軟に臨機応変 七変化が勝ち
Being flexible and adaptive, the master of disguise wins!
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
Because in reality, I'm crazy
孔雀たちはそう
Just like peacocks
ここぞというとき…
When the time is right...
ここぞというとき美を見せるんです
Wait till the time is right to show their beauty
五臓六腑 満身邁進 願望は痩身麗人
Our bodies and beings struggle on, desiring to be slim and beautiful
誘惑多発だし...
There are lots of temptations, after all...
だからやけに意志砕けちゃうんです
Which is why we get so terribly distracted sometimes
ヤバ まさか赤点!? いや ギリクリア!
Crap, is that a red mark? Ah, no, I'm just barely in the clear!
それだけでなんか全能感
And just that makes you feel so almighty
大事なのは自分 認めてくこと
The most important thing is to accept yourself
自分を許さなきゃ 他人も許せない
If you don't forgive yourself, you can't forgive others either
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当にcrazy
Because truthfully, I'm crazy!
白鳥たちはそう
Swans, you know,
見えないとこでバタ足するんです
flutter their legs where they can't be seen.
本能に従順 忠実 翻弄も重々承知
True to my instincts, though constantly ridiculed,
前途洋々だし... だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
my future is bright... so I'll rest sometimes!
Wow! Gimana? How was it?
Wow! How was it? How was it?
Wasn't the gondola, and the bazooka, and everything, very cool?
We had so many songs, but... there's still more!
Here's the long awaited...
Here's the long-awaited...
グッズ紹介！今回も生誕グッズがあります。Yeah.
Merchandise reveal! We have birthday merch this time too. Yeah.
まずは、こちらですね。青い炎の孔雀ラバーマット。
First up, we have this: Peafowl of the Blue Flame Rubber Mat!
えー、Peafowl of the Blue Flame Rubber Mat. Ini seperti...
The Peafowl of the Blue Flame Rubber Mat. This is, like...
yang dijanjikan ya, just like how we said earlier...
promised, just like how we said earlier...
totally no spoiler, made by Pochi-mama!
So many people missed out on the previous rubber mats/desk mats, and so we have another one!
And for those of you who already have that rubber mat, well, ini ada lagi...
And for those of you who already have that rubber mat, well, here's another one...
beda, it's different. Yay!
different, it's different. Yay!
And along with the rubber mat, we have...
the tapestry! Yay!
Ini kalian tidak tergoreng ya? Kalian tidak tergoreng. Gak apa-apa kegoreng dikit, pokoknya keren.
You won't get roasted, okay? You won't get roasted. Even if you get roasted a bit, it's cool.
Yeah, sesuai tema live dari kali ini, we have...
Yeah, in line with the theme of this live show, we have...
青い炎の孔雀タペストリー。
the Peafowl of the Blue Flame Tapestry!
Gambarnya sama tapi kali ini edisi tapestry ya, dibuat oleh Pochi-mama juga.
The illustration is the same but this is the tapestry version, also drawn by Pochi-mama.
Silakan dicek out, silakan dicek out.
Please check it out, please check it out.
Dan...
And...
続いてはこちらですね。Mana nih? Lanjutannya buat kalian yang suka...
next up is this one. Where is it? The next is for those of you who like...
minimalist design. For those of you who like designs that are more minimalistic in nature...
minimalist designs. For those of you who like designs that are more minimalistic in nature...
We have Blueming Flame Coaster. We have 咲き誇る青い炎のコースター。
We have the Blueming Flame Coaster. We have the Blooming Blue Flame Coaster.
Yes!
And pokoknya temanya itu cocok banget sama tapestry-nya dan juga rubber mat-nya yang tadi ya, ilustrasi Pochi-mama.
And the theme fits perfectly with the tapestry and also the rubber mat from earlier, illustrated by Pochi-mama.
Jadi mendingan masukkan ke keranjang sekarang juga. Eh, belum bisa ya? Ya sudahlah gak apa-apa.
So you'd better add it to your cart right away. Oh, you can't yet? Well, that's fine.
And then next one...
さらに、こちら！
Furthermore, this!
Ada juga, seperti biasa, ada voice.
We also have, as usual, a voice pack.
Kali ini karena Reine suka sekali sushi, because I love sushi so much, sushi daisuki Reine-ga membuat...
This time, because Reine loves sushi so much, sushi-loving Reine has made...
Secret Sushi Strategy / シークレット寿司作戦 voice pack.
the "Secret Sushi Strategy" voice pack!
Untuk kalian yang suka sushi juga mungkin ya.
Maybe for those of you who also like sushi.
Let's go!
最後に、フルセットを購入いただいた方には...
Finally, for those who purchase the full set...
buat yang beli full set akan ada...
for those who buy the full set, there will be...
数量限定で直筆メッセージと箔押し複製サイン入りポストカードがついてきます。
a limited-edition postcard with a handwritten message and a foil-stamped copied autograph.
Akan ada limited-edition postcard yang ada message dan tanda tangan dari Reine juga. There's going to be a limited edition postcard...
There will be a limited-edition postcard with a message and autograph from Reine too, there's going to be a limited-edition postcard...
buat yang beli... eh kok Indonesia lagi? For those people who buy the full set! Let's go!
for those who buy... wait, why Indonesian again? For those people who buy the full set! Let's go!
え、通常版は箔押し複製サインとメッセージ入り...
And the regular version has a foil-stamped copied autograph and message...
何だっけ？ ポストカードがついてきます。
What was it? Postcard included!
Yang beli biasa juga akan ada postcard yang ada message dan sign ya. Oke.
Those who buy the regular set will also get a postcard with a message and signature. Okay.
And then...
next up, I'm going to introduce...
my new song! Yes.
Well, I don't know, this is my first...
It's my first time doing this genre...
...so I'm a little bit shy.
It's a little bit different...
...from what I usually sing,
so I hope you guys can, gimana ya...
so I hope you guys can... how should I say...
...if it could resonate with you guys...
...even for a little, I would be so happy.
こんなジャンルの曲をするの初めてでした。
It's my first time performing a song in this genre.
And...
...だからね、ちょっとシャイです。
...so, I'm a bit shy.
And yeah, well basically...
...being placed in a box you don't fit...
...it sucks, right?
And this is some sort of, you know...
...it's a song of self-acceptance.
And sometimes your flaws are what makes you, you.
And even if you're broken, it's fine,
and no one else's opinions should change that.
And... Okay.
とにかく、自分をありのままを...
Anyway, it's a song that says...
...愛していいよ、って曲です。
..."It's okay to love yourself just as you are."
じゃあ、あの、これから準備するので待っててね！
Well, I'm going to get ready now, so please wait!
Please wait, 'cause I'm gonna prepare!
I got a surprise!
Yay! Bye-bye!
PAVOLIA REINE MEMBERSHIP PROMOTIONAL VIDEO "The Royaltea"
Attention please!
Are you somebody looking for a new experience?
Or are you by any chance a MERAKyats...
...who just can't wait for when...
...I'm going to implement a certain feature?
Or are you simply wanting to get a head start...
...with flexing using super amazing badges...
...and cute emojis?
Well, you're in luck!
My name is Pavolia Reine,
and I'm going to be here explaining briefly...
...what is going on with Reine's membership.
(That is mine, by the way.)
At The Royaltea,
our super advanced magical technology...
...grants you badge flexing rights,
which you can constantly show off...
...every time you're here with us.
We also make sure to provide you...
...with utmost care and sense of belonging...
...by granting you a one-of-a-kind experience...
...with cute emojis.
At just the right price, you'll be able...
...to join our exclusive Royaltea parties,
which also means membership-exclusive streams,
in which we can have various talks,
play games together,
and do other miscellaneous member involvements.
Like what, you might ask?
Only one way to find out.
And lastly, safety isn't guaranteed,
but it is...
safety IS GUARANTEED GUARANTEED GUARANTEED...
...development training in which we aim to...
...build a community of people...
...who like living dangerously.
Attention please! Are you somebody looking for a new experience?
We welcome everybody with open arms...
...to join The Royaltea.
hey, hey, hey
(never, never, never gonna figure it out)
(never gonna figure it out)
Wake up, another bloody monday
Say things i never wanted to say
Up in arms, who can i please? you?
Livin' day by day
Wake up, another bloody monday
Rinse and repeat until it's sunday
Hold it, so frustrating
Ya know, i can't do it no more
I'll say
No good, down to the core
Hear you knockin', beatin' down my door
Yeah, loud, scream and shout
But i'll never change it now
I'm just too much, but not enough...
...to please you, right?
(no, i'm never, never gonna —)
Your idea of ideals
That you're screaming in my ear
I'm just so broken, yeah
(never, never, never gonna figure it out)
hey, hey
I'll stop me
Oh, now we'll figure it out
hey, hey
never, never, never gonna figure it out
You want me to know what i just don't know
Mold me into her? into him? no
Little that you know, i'm just me, let it go
Lock me inside a pen of your perfection...
correction
Am i what you like now?
Don't tell me what
What to do, what to say, what to think
About everything, but did you ever think?
I'll say
Good with bein' so bad
What's the issue?
I'll screw up again
Yell out, scream and shout
But i'll never change it now
I'm just too much, but not enough...
...to please you, right?
(no, i'm never, never gonna —)
Your idea of ideals
broken, yeah, yeah...
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
Comfortable and pathetic
I like it that way, get it?
You're brutal, judgmental, it's never that simple
But I still want...
To meet your harsh criteria
Too bad I'm never gonna
I'm never gonna fit!
Oh, no!
One, two, three, go!
Yell out, scream and shout
But I'll never change it now
I'm just too much but not enough to please you, right?
Never, never gonna...
Your idea of ideals
That you're screaming in my ear
I'm just so broken...
Never, never, never gonna figure it out!
Hey! Hey!
I'll stop me!
I'll never figure it out!
Hey! Hey!
Never, never, never gonna figure it out!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Never gonna figure it out!
Hey! Hey!